Thank you.
You
I want to be like the Serrano
Even if life is as usual
I can't stop thinking about those extreme romances
Just like Quentin Tarantino
Say yeah yeah yeah
I heard them say
True love is a accumulation of time
Blah blah blah
If you can't get it, you should just leave
Keep it cool
Ha ha ha
They say love a person
Just ask yourself if you accept marriage
Don't know what kind of stupid marriage
But I'm willing to be in love with him
I'm willing, I'm willing
Anyway, it's almost
Just one second, one second
I'm willing
Yeah, I'm willing
Even if there's an earthquake, a tsunami, a terrorist attack
The earth will lose its gravity
I'm willing, I'm willing
To face it with him
The moment of collapse of human civilization
Let's face the world together
Fly off to the past
Look at your eyes
It's all twisted
I don't care what day it is tomorrow
What time it is
That last sip of cold
I will definitely leave it to you
Walk around for you
I don't know where to apply
To make you wear makeup
Not until the last minute
I can't look at the dandruff and dirt
Cover your face
After death, I'm a lonely ghost
And you must become
Injured
So to speak, life is a long journey
I just want to dive into your ocean
I'm going down to get close to your heart
Become a deep sea of tears
From now on, I'm deaf and blind
I can still feel you around me
Just like the first time I saw you
I can't open my eyes anymore
How did you touch me?
Thanks to the earth
Thanks to other people, I've become a ghost
Otherwise, how could you shed tears
And see me again?
I love the king
If there's a distance between the sword and the throat, it's 0.01cm
But if the position of the sword burns
I'm in love with her
In other words, I can't die because of that sword
Because I've decided
In this case, I'll tell a lie
I often tell a lie in my life
But I think that's the most perfect
They say to love a person
Just ask yourself if you accept marriage
I don't know what kind of high-class marriage
But I'm willing to make a relationship with him
I'm willing to
Yeah, I'm willing to
Anyway, it's almost just a second kill and a heart attack
I'm willing to
Even if the earthquake, the tsunami, the storm attacks
You will lose all your strength
I'm willing to
Face the moment when we are together
Dream of his human civilization
I'm willing to face it
I'm willing to be strong
I'm willing to believe
I'm willing to break through
I'm willing to cannot hide
I'm willing to make changes
I'm willing to be very confident
That marriage is always easy
That I always love
I'm willing to go
I'm willing to take the easy path
I can walk it
I don't look far away
Not today or tomorrow